Bagus Candra Budi Laksana

Bobotsari, Purbalingga, Jawa Tengah

■ 085229931237 | Secondra and a candra and

Personal Profile

Hi, I'm Chandra I really like the world of programming and am currently learning the Golang programming language, also learning about Linux, started programming 3 years ago, gained 2 years of experience in making quite large projects, such as Komtim, Komship, and Kompack, have a high enthusiasm for learning especially about new thing

Skills

Programming PHP, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Golang, SQL.

Soft Skills Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation

Work Experience

Komerce Purbalingga, Indonesia

Backend Developer Mar 2020 - Current

- Create landing page komerce and maintenance landing pages, using Laravel Bootstrap
- Create a customer service landing page for Komerce, using laravel bootstrap
- Create an advertiser landing page for Komerce, using laravel bootstrap
- Create a team API for internal management and commercial partners, using Laravel and several third parties to develop the application, third parties like xendit for payments, firebase for notifications, qontak for register notifications, for deployment using server VPS
- Created a komship API, a new product regarding helping thousands of people run their business, has implemented several expeditions such as SICEPAT, IDEXPRESS, JNE, using third party APIs, such as xendit for payments and withdrawals, qontak for registering komship partners, firebase for expedition ticketing notifications, APIs (JNE, SICEPAT, IDEXPRESS) (change order status, track trips, calculate postage payments, pickup orders), for deployment using the GCP server
- · Kompack development, in terms of goods pickup, and payment gateways, using lumens, for deployment using the GCP server

SaungMakaryo Purbalingga, Indonesia

Web Developer

Sept 2019 - Mar 2020

- · Create an ambedoc website and maintain the ambedoc website from display updates, using wordpress elementor
- Make the main website saungmakaryo, and maintain the website, using wordpress elementor
- Create a naadif website using wordpress elementor and promote it using facebook ads

Interests_

Drawing I always give vent to my emotions in drawing, to satisfy my emotions

Video Games I've always had the game gene. I mostly play on my phone and sometimes on my PC.

Gym I exercise to maintain my endurance, 3x a week.

Music I enjoy almost all types of music may it be pop, K-Pop, rap, and J-Pop.

Education

SMK NEGERI 2 PURBALINGGA

Purbalingga, Ind

Software Enginering

Sept 2016 - 2019

- · Never participated in a district-level website creation competition, got an expectation rating of 1
- never participated in a national level competition at Muhammadiyah University, created an online web store and won first place

Languages _

Indonesia Native proficiency

DECEMBER 23, 2022